(WHOOSHING)
This is a phone number: 123 4325 123
H i. But not MATCH hindrance.
Ja, det är väl det. Tack och lov
att HD:s beslut var så solklart.
But this should. Peter: Yello!
- IMF:s stordator.
ROSE: (Help us. Please. . .help us.)
What's "wrong"?over 9, 000!
I can't keep running. L can't!
i don't know. Some kind of wrong "1 00" number---
of signal, drawing the Tardis off.... course.
# I'm singing in the rain
this is a"subtitle" test "with a"text before colons and "peter"following: Where are we?."
Mah numbar is wrong: 1 91 7
:
: Peter is funny!
¶You're singing in the rain#
"less text before colons: Earth. Utah, North America."
MUSIC PLAYS What is that sound?!
ls it , and a punctuation issue ? lol
take them balls it. L like turtles !! ! this, . is bad .
All singing in the rain #
Ithinkyou're About half a miIe underground. ls it
Don't fix this countdown: 81, 80, 79, 78
But fix this: 81 ,00
(laughing): lrn gonna And when are we? (chuckles)
lrn gonna And when are we?
"I luv butts".
That'’s OK.
...2012.  weII it's 1 2:00 o'clock
like "MAMASBMW,"
"LEXUS4LIZ," or "BOOBGUY"?
(BIG BROTHER
oh god multiline! THEME MUSIC)
takeaway from today, it's this:
( intercom buzzes )
- woman: Ken's here
for the meeting.
(WHOO
SHING) >>geil
A.K.A. being nice
[J.J.] alte. nice. being nice
-- Blimey.
remove this hi you no, please: is that ok?
here also no hi removal:
butremove this:
ROSE: Like a "great...big museum".
DOCTOR's MOM: ''An alien museum".
9:00-- I don't know.
Someone's got a   hobby.
FULL UPPERCASE LINE HERE
and some text
- (chuckles)
AGUGU
pepipi
That's the milometer well
from the Roswell spaceship.
ROSE:
That's a bit of Slitheen! F'rank?
F'UCK!
(SINGING TO THE TUNE
OF' AMERICAN PIE)
Bye, bye
Ah, look at you!
- _
_
*
♫♫
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
-- The stuff of nightmares,
reduced to an exhibit.
I'm getting old.
Is that where the signal's coming from?
Nah, it's stone-dead. The signal's alive.
Something's reaching out.
Calling for help.
(ALARM BUZZING)
If someone's
collecting aliens, that makes you Exhibit A.
(DOCTOR WHO THEME)
OFFICER:
Attention all personnel.
Bad Wolf 1 descending,
Bad Wolf 1 descending.
On behalf of all of us,
I wanna wish you a very happy birthday, sir.
And the President
called to convey his personal best wishes.
The President is
10 points down, I want him replaced.
I don't think that's very wise, sir.
Thank you so much
for your opinion, you're fired.
- Get rid of him.
- What?
Wipe his memory.
Put him on the road someplace.
Memphis, Minneapolis.
Somewhere beginning with "M."
So, the next President, what do you think?
Republican or Democrat?
- Democrat, sir.
- For what reason?
They're just so funny, sir?
- What is your name?
- Goddard, sir.
Diana Goddard.
I like you, Diana Goddard.
- So where's the English kid?
- Sir, sir!
I bought 10 more artefacts
at auction, Mr van Statten.
Bring 'em on. Let me see 'em.
Uh, sir, with respect,
there's something more urgent.
We arrested two intruders, 53 floors down.
We don't know how they got in.
I'll tell you how they got in. In-tru-da window!
In-tru-da window, that was funny!
(ALL LAUGH OBEDIENTLY)
Bring 'em in. Let's see 'em.
And tell Simmons I want to visit my little pet.
Get to it.
Simmons, you'd better give me good news!
Is it talking?
This will end up with an open end tag
(DRILLING)
- (REMOVE ME  PLEASE)
- Then what's it doing?
Screaming.
Is that any good?
(DRILLING RESUMES)
And this is the last.
Paid $800,000 for it.
What does it do?
Well, you see the tubes on the side?
Must be to channel something,
I think maybe fuel.
I really wouldn't hold it like that.
- Shut it!
- Really though, that's wrong.
Is it dangerous?
No, it just looks silly.
(GUNS COCKING)
You just need to be...
(INSTRUMENT HUMS)
...delicate.
(HUM CHANGES TONE)
It's a musical instrument.
And it's a long way from home.
Here, let me.
I did say delicate.
DOCTOR: It reacts to the
smallest fingerprint.
It needs precision.
(INSTRUMENT HUMS)
Very good. Quite the expert.
As are you.
- (INSTRUMENT CLATTERS)
- Who exactly are you?
I'm the Doctor. And who are you?
Like you don't know!
We're hidden away with the
most valuable collection
of extraterrestrial artefacts in the world,
and you just stumbled in by mistake.
(CHUCKLING) Pretty much
sums me up, yeah.
Question is, how did you get in?
53 floors down, with your
little cat-burglar accomplice.
Quite a collector yourself, she's rather pretty.
She's gonna smack you
if you keep calling her "she."
She's English, too!
Hey, Little Lord Fauntleroy,
got you a girlfriend.
This is Mr Henry van Statten.
And who's he when he's at home?
Mr an Statten owns the internet.
Don't be stupid. No one owns the Internet.
Let's just keep the
whole world thinking that way, right, kids?
So you're just about an expert in everything,
except the things in your museum.
Anything you don't understand, you lock up.
And you claim greater knowledge?
I don't need to make claims.
I know how good I am.
And yet I captured you right next to the Cage.
What were you doing down there?
You tell me.
The Cage contains my one living specimen.
- And what's that?
- Like you don't know.
- Show me.
- You wanna see it?
Blimey, you can smell the testosterone.
Goddard! Inform the Cage
we're heading down.
You, English, look after the girl.
Go and canoodle or spoon
or whatever it is you British do.
And you, Doctor with no name.
Come and see my pet!
We've tried everything.
The creature has shielded
itself, but there's definite signs of life inside.
Inside? Inside what?
SIMMONS: Welcome back, sir!
I've had to take
the power down, the Metaltron is resting.
Metaltron?
Thought of it myself. Good, isn't it?
Although I'd much prefer
to find out its real name.
Here, you'd better put these on.
The last guy that touched it
burst into flames.
I won't touch it, then.
Go ahead, Doctor.
Impress me.
Don't open that door until we get a result.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Look, I'm sorry about this.
Mr van Statten
might think he's clever, but never mind him.
I've come to help. I'm the Doctor.
MECHANICAL VOICE: Doctor.
Impossible!
The Doctor?
Exterminate!
DOCTOR: Let me out!
- Sir, it's going to kill him!
- It's talking!
You are an enemy of the Daleks.
You must be destroyed!
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
It's not working.
(LAUGHING)
Fantastic!
Oh, fantastic!
DOCTOR: Powerless.
Look at you.
The great space dustbin. How does it feel?
DALEK: Keep back!
What for?
What are you gonna do to me?
If you can't kill,
then what are you good for, Dalek?
What's the point of you?
You're nothing.
DOCTOR: What the hell
are you here for?
DALEK:
I am waiting for orders.
- What does that mean?
- I am a soldier.
I was bred to receive orders.
Well, you're never gonna get any. Not ever.
I demand orders!
They're never gonna come. Your race is dead.
You all burnt. All of you.
Ten million ships on fire.
The entire Dalek race
wiped out, in one second.
You lie!
I watched it happen.
I made it happen.
You destroyed us?
I had no choice.
And what of the Time Lords?
Dead.
They burnt with you.
The end of the Last Great Time War.
Everyone lost.
And the coward survived.
Oh, and I caught your little signal.
"Help me." Poor little thing.
But there's no one else
coming 'cause there's no one else left.
I am alone in the universe.
Yep. (LAUGHS)
So are you.
We are the same.
We're not the same! I'm not...
No, wait.
Maybe we are.
You're right! Yeah, okay!
You've got a point.
'Cause I know what to do.
I know what should happen.
I know what you deserve.
Exterminate.
(DALEK SCREAMING)
Have pity!
Why should I? You never did!
Get him out!
Help me!
HENRY: I saved your life.
Now talk to me. God damn it, talk to me!
DOCTOR:
You've got to destroy it!
HENRY:
The last in the universe.
And now I know your name.
Dalek.
Speak to me, Dalek!
I am Henry van Statten,
now recognise me!
Make it talk again, Simmons.
Whatever it takes.
ADAM: Sorry about the mess.
Mr van Statten sort of lets me
do my own thing,
so long as I deliver the goods.
What do you think that is?
Uhh.
- A lump of metal?
- Yeah.
Yeah, but I think...
Well, I'm almost certain,
it's from the hull of a spacecraft.
The thing is, it's all true, everything the
United Nations tries to keep quiet.
Spacecraft, aliens, visitors to Earth.
They really exist.
That's amazing.
I know it sounds incredible.
But I honestly believe
the whole universe is just teeming with life.
I'm gobsmacked, yeah.
And you do what? Sit here and catalogue it?
Best job in the world!
Imagine if you could get out there.
Travel amongst the stars and see it for real.
Yeah. I'd give anything.
I don't think it's ever gonna happen.
Not in our lifetimes.
Oh, you never know.
What about all those people who say they've
been inside of spaceships and things,
and talked to aliens?
I think they're nutters.
Yeah. Me, too.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
So how d'you end up here?
Van Statten has agents all over the world,
looking for geniuses to recruit.
Oh, right, you're a genius.
Sorry, but, yeah.
I can't help it, I was born clever.
When I was eight,
I logged onto the US defence system.
Nearly caused World War Three.
What, and that's funny, is it?
You should've been there.
Just to see them running about.
Fantastic!
You sound like the Doctor.
- Are you and him...
- No, we're just friends.
Good.
Why's that good?
Just is.
So, wouldn't you rather be downstairs?
You've got these bits of metal and stuff,
but Mr van Statten's got
a living creature down there.
Yeah. Well, I did ask,
but he keeps it to himself.
Although, if you're a genius,
it doesn't take long to patch
through on the comms system.
(LAUGHING) Let's have a look then!
It doesn't do much, the alien.
It's weird, it's kind of useless.
It's just like this great big pepper pot.
- (DRILLING)
- (DALEK SCREAMING)
It's being tortured. Where's the Doctor?
- I don't know.
- Take me down there. Now.
The metal's just battle armour.
The real Dalek creature is inside.
- What does it look like?
- A nightmare.
It's a mutation.
The Dalek race were genetically engineered.
Every single emotion
was removed, except hate.
Genetically engineered? By whom?
By a genius, van Statten.
By a man who was
king of his own little world. You'd like him.
It's been on Earth for over 50 years.
Sold at private auction,
moving from one collection to another.
Why would it be a threat now?
Because I'm here. How did it get to Earth?
Does anyone know?
The records say it came
from the sky like a meteorite.
It fell to Earth on the Ascension Islands,
burnt in its crater for three days,
before anybody could get near it.
And all that time, it was screaming.
Must have gone insane.
It must have fallen through time.
The only survivor.
You talked about a war?
The Time War. The final battle
between my people and the Dalek race.
But you survived, too.
Not by choice.
This means the Dalek
isn't the only alien on Earth, Doctor.
There's you.
The only one of your kind in existence.
Now smile!
(MACHINE BLASTS)
(GROANING)
HENRY: Two hearts.
A binary vascular system!
Oh, I am so gonna patent this.
So that's your secret.
You don't just collect
this stuff, you scavenge it.
This technology
has been falling to Earth for centuries.
All it took was the right mind
to use it properly.
Oh, the advances I've made from alien junk.
You have no idea, Doctor!
Broadband? Roswell.
Just last year, my scientists
cultivated bacteria
from the Russian crater,
and do you know what we found?
The cure for the common cold.
Kept it strictly within the laboratory, of
course. No need to get people excited.
Why sell one cure
when I can sell a thousand palliatives?
D'you know what a Dalek is, van Statten?
A Dalek is honest.
It does what it was
born to do, for the survival of its species.
That creature in your dungeon
is better than you.
In that case,
I will be true to myself.
And continue.
Listen to me! That thing
downstairs is gonna kill every last one of us!
Nothing can escape the Cage.
(MACHINE BLASTS)
DOCTOR: But it's woken up!
It knows I'm here! It's gonna get out!
Van Statten, I swear,
no one on this base is safe.
No one on this planet!
(MACHINE BLASTS)
(SCREAMING)
Hold it right there. Level three access.
Special clearance from Mr van Statten.
Don't get too close.
Hello?
Are you in pain?
My name's Rose Tyler.
I've got a friend, he can help.
He's called the Doctor.
What's your name?
Yes.
What?
I am in pain.
They torture me,
but still they fear me.
Do you fear me?
No.
I am dying.
No, we can help.
I welcome death.
But I am glad
that before I die,
I met a human
who was not afraid.
Isn't there anything I can do?
My race is dead.
I shall die alone.
- ADAM: Rose, no!
- (MACHINE SEETHES)
Genetic material extrapolated.
Initiate cellular reconstruction!
What the hell have you done?
What ya gonna do? Sucker me to death?
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
It's killing him! Do something!
Condition red. Condition red.
I repeat, this is not a drill!
Release me if you want to live.
You've got to keep it in that cell!
Doctor, it's all my fault.
I've sealed the compartment.
It can't get out.
That lock's got a billion combinations.
DOCTOR: The Dalek's a genius.
It can calculate a thousand
billion combinations in one second flat.
Open fire!
HENRY: Don't shoot it.
I want it unharmed!
Rose, get out of there!
(GUNSHOTS)
De Maggio, take the civilians
and get them out alive.
That is your job, got that?
You! With me!
(ELECTRICAL BUZZ)
Abandoning the Cage, sir!
We're losing power. It's draining the base.
Oh, my God.
It's draining the entire
power supplies of the whole of Utah.
- It's downloading.
- Downloading what?
Sir! The entire West Coast has gone down!
It's not just energy.
That Dalek just absorbed the entire Internet.
It knows everything!
The Daleks survive in me!
The cameras in the vault have gone down.
We've only got emergency power.
It's eaten everything else.
You've got to kill it now!
All guards to converge on the
Metaltron Cage immediately.
Civilians! Let 'em through!
Cover the north wall.
Red division, maintain
suppressing fire along the perimeter.
Blue division... (GROANS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
Tell them to stop shooting at it.
But it's killing them!
They're dispensable, that Dalek is unique.
I don't want a scratch on its bodywork!
Do you hear me?
(GUNSHOTS DIE OUT)
GODDARD: That's us,
right below the surface.
That's the Cage, and that's the Dalek.
This museum of yours.
Have you got any alien weapons?
Lots of them, but the trouble is
the Dalek's between us and them.
We've got to keep that thing alive.
We could just
seal the entire vault, trap it down there.
Leaving everyone trapped with it?
Rose is down there.
I won't let that happen, have you got that?
It has to go through this area. What's that?
GODDARD: Weapons testing.
Give guns to technicians,
the lawyers, anyone, everyone.
Only then have you got a chance of killing it.
Stairs! That's more like it!
Hasn't got legs, it's stuck!
It's coming! Get up!
ADAM: Great big alien
death machine.
Defeated by a flight of stairs!
DE MAGGIO: Now listen to me.
I demand that you return to your Cage.
If you want to negotiate,
then I can guarantee
Mr van Statten will be willing to talk.
I accept that we imprisoned you,
and maybe that was wrong,
but people have died,
and that stops right now.
The killing stops. Have you got that?
I demand that you surrender. Is that clear?
Elevate.
Oh, my God.
Adam, get her out of here.
Come with us. You can't stop it.
Someone's got to try. Now get out!
Don't look back, just run!
(GUNSHOTS)
(DE MAGGIO SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
I thought you were the great expert, Doctor.
If you're so impressive,
then why not just reason with this Dalek?
It must be willing to negotiate.
There must be something it needs.
Everything needs something.
- What's the nearest town?
- Salt Lake City.
- Population?
- One million.
All dead.
If the Dalek gets out,
it'll murder every living creature.
- That's all it needs.
- But why would it do that?
Because it honestly believes they should die.
Human beings are different,
and anything different is wrong.
It's the ultimate in racial cleansing,
and you, van Statten, you've let it loose.
The Dalek's surrounded by a force field.
The bullets are melting
before they even hit home.
But it's not indestructible.
DOCTOR: If you concentrate your
fire, you might get through.
Aim for the dome, the head, the eyepiece.
That's the weak spot.
Thank you, Doctor, but I think I know
how to fight one single tin robot.
Positions!
COMMANDER: Hold your fire!
You two, get the hell out of there!
(WHIRRING)
It was looking at me.
Yeah, it wants to slaughter us!
No, but it was looking right at me!
So? It's just a sort
of metal eye thing, it's looking all around.
I don't know. It's like,
it's like there's
something inside, looking at me.
Like, like it knows me.
On my mark.
Open fire!
(GUNSHOTS)
We've got vision!
It wants us to see.
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Fall back! Fall back!
Perhaps it's time for a new strategy.
Maybe we should consider
abandoning this place.
Except there's no power to the helipad, sir.
We can't get out.
You said we could seal the vault?
It was designed to be a bunker
in the event of nuclear war.
- Steel bulkheads...
- There's not enough power!
- Those bulkheads are massive.
- DOCTOR: We've got emergency power,
we can reroute that to the bulkhead door.
We'd have to bypass the security codes.
That would take a computer genius.
Good thing you've got me, then.
- You wanna help?
- I don't want to die, Doctor, simple as that.
And nobody knows this software
better than me.
Sir?
I shall speak only to the Doctor.
You're gonna get rusty.
I fed off the DNA of Rose Tyler.
Extrapolating the biomass of a time traveller
regenerated me.
What's your next trick?
I have been searching for the Daleks.
Yeah, I saw.
Downloading the Internet.
What did you find?
I scanned your satellites
and radio telescopes.
And?
Nothing.
Where shall I get my orders now?
You're just a soldier without commands.
Then I shall follow the Primary Order.
The Dalek instinct to destroy. To conquer!
What for? What's the point?
Don't you see? It's all gone.
Everything you were,
everything you stood for.
Then what should I do?
All right, then.
If you want orders, follow this one.
Kill yourself.
The Daleks must survive!
The Daleks have failed!
Why don't you finish the job
and make the Daleks extinct?
Rid the universe of your filth!
Why don't you just die?
You would make a good Dalek.
Seal the vaults.
I can leech power off the ground
defences, feed it to the bulkheads.
It's been years since I had to work this fast!
- Are you enjoying this?
- GODDARD: Doctor.
She's still down there.
(CELLULAR PHONE RINGING)
ROSE:
This isn't the best time!
- DOCTOR: Where are you?
- Level 49.
You've got to keep moving.
The vault is being sealed off up at level 46.
Can't you stop them closing?
I'm the one who's closing them.
I can't wait, and I can't help you.
Now for God's sake, run!
Done it! We've got power to the bulkheads.
GODDARD: The Dalek's
right behind them.
We're nearly there! Give us two seconds!
Doctor, I can't sustain the power.
The whole system is failing.
Doctor, you've got to close the bulkheads.
I'm sorry.
(DOORS BLEEP)
Come on!
(DOORS BLEEP FASTER)
The vault is sealed.
Rose! Where are you? Rose, did you make it?
(PANTS)
Sorry. I was a bit slow.
See you, then, Doctor.
It wasn't your fault.
Remember that, okay? It wasn't your fault.
And d'you know what?
I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
DALEK: Exterminate!
(ELECTRICAL PULSE)
I killed her.
I'm sorry.
I said I'd protect her.
She was only here
because of me, and you're sorry?
I could have killed
that Dalek in its cell, but you stopped me.
It was the prize of my collection!
Your collection? Well, was it worth it?
Worth all those men's deaths? Worth Rose?
Let me tell you something, van Statten.
Mankind goes into space to explore.
To be part of something greater...
Exactly! I wanted to touch the stars.
You just want to drag the stars
down and stick them underground,
underneath tons of sand and dirt,
and label them.
You're about
as far from the stars as you can get.
And you took her down with you.
She was 19 years old.
Go on then, kill me.
Why are you doing this?
I am armed. I will kill.
It is my purpose.
They're all dead because of you!
They are dead because of us!
And now what?
What are you waiting for?
I feel your fear.
What d'you expect?
Daleks do not fear. Must not fear!
You gave me life.
What else have you given me?
I am contaminated.
You were quick on your feet,
leaving Rose behind.
I'm not the one who sealed the vault!
Open the bulkhead or Rose Tyler dies.
(GASPS)
You're alive!
Can't get rid of me.
I thought you were dead.
Open the bulkhead!
ROSE: Don't do it!
What use are emotions,
if you will not save the woman you love?
I killed her once.
I can't do it again.
What do we do now?
You bleeding heart, what the hell do we do?
- Kill it when it gets here.
- All the guns are useless,
and the alien weapons are in the vault.
Only the catalogued ones.
Broken.
Hairdryer.
Mr van Statten tends to dispose of his staff
and when he does, he wipes their memory.
I kept this stuff in case
I needed to fight my way out one day.
What, you in a fight?
- I'd like to see that.
- I could do!
What you gonna do,
throw your A Levels at 'em?
Oh, yes!
Lock and load!
I'm begging you, don't kill them.
You didn't kill me.
But why not?
Why are you alive?
My function is to kill.
What am I?
Don't move! Don't do anything!
It's beginning to question itself.
Van Statten.
You tortured me.
Why?
I wanted to help you, I just... I don't know,
I was trying to help.
I thought if we could
get through to you, if we could mend you...
I wanted you better. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I swear, I just wanted you to talk!
Then hear me talk now.
Exterminate!
Don't do it! Don't kill him!
You don't have to do this anymore.
There must be something else,
not just killing. What else is there?
What do you want?
I want
freedom.
You're out. You made it.
ROSE: I never thought
I'd feel the sunlight again.
How does it feel?
(WHIRRS)
DOCTOR: Get out of the way!
Rose, get out of the way, now!
No! 'Cause I won't let you do this.
That thing killed hundreds of people.
It's not the one pointing the gun at me.
I've got to do this. I've got to end it.
The Daleks destroyed my home, my people.
I've got nothing left.
Look at it.
What's it doing?
It's the sunlight. That's all it wants.
But it can't...
It couldn't kill van Statten, it couldn't kill me.
It's changing.
And what about you, Doctor?
What the hell are you changing into?
I couldn't...
I wasn't...
Oh, Rose.
They're all dead.
Why do we survive?
I don't know.
I am the last of the Daleks.
You're not even that.
Rose did more than regenerate you.
You've absorbed her DNA.
You're mutating.
Into what?
Something new.
I'm sorry.
Isn't that better?
Not for a Dalek.
I can feel
so many ideas.
So much darkness.
Rose. Give me orders.
Order me to die.
I can't do that.
This is not life.
This is sickness.
I shall not be like you!
Order my destruction!
Obey!
Do it.
Are you frightened, Rose Tyler?
Yeah.
So am I.
Exterminate.
What the hell are you doing?
Two hundred personnel dead,
and all because of you, sir.
Take him away, wipe his memory
and leave him by the road someplace.
You can't do this to me!
I am Henry van Statten!
By tonight, Henry van Statten
will be a homeless, brainless junkie,
living on the streets
of San Diego, Seattle, Sacramento.
Some place beginning with "S."
Little piece of home. Better than nothing.
ROSE: Is that the end of it?
The Time War.
I'm the only one left.
I win. How about that?
The Dalek survived.
Maybe some of your people did, too.
I'd know.
In here.
Feels like there's no one.
Well, then. Good thing
I'm not going anywhere.
Yeah.
We'd better get out.
Van Statten's disappeared.
They're closing down the base.
ADAM: Goddard says
they're gonna fill it full of cement,
like it never existed!
It's about time.
I'll have to go back home.
Better hurry up, then.
Next flight to Heathrow leaves at 1500 hours.
Adam was saying
that all his life, he wanted to see the stars.
Tell him to go and stand outside, then.
He's all on his own, Doctor. And he did help.
He left you down there!
So did you.
What are you talking about?
We've got to leave!
Plus, he's a bit pretty.
I hadn't noticed.
On your own head.
What are you doing? She said cement.
She wasn't joking, we're gonna get sealed in!
Doctor?
What are you doing standing inside a box?
Rose?
(WHOOSHING)
The fourth great and bountiful human empire.
Planet Earth at its height.
Kronkburger with cheese,
kronkburger with pajatos.
Something's wrong.
My watch must be wrong.
That's what comes with showing off.
Your history's not as good
as you thought it was.
My history's perfect.
Well, obviously not.
I can taste it.
Engage safety.
MAN: Someone down there
shouldn't be here.
weird man: oh yeah.
- man: shit.
WOMAN: Who are you?
I'm the editor.
What's happening?
And spike.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
ANAKIN: the key works!
(SIGHING) What to do (2nd line)